Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Archives Information File, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
- Box: 88, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Amendments to West Virginia Unemployment Compensation Law, 1967; Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
    Author: West Virginia Department of Employment Security
    Notes: March 27, 1967
  - Item 2: Handbook for Employers, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Handbook for Employers, 1967; Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Unemployment Benefit Entitlement Study, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: West Virginia's Unemployment Compensation Law, Publication (Box 88, Folder 7)
- Box: 88, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Wyoming Statistical Review, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
    Author: Wyoming Employment Security Commission
  - Item 2: Wyoming Employment Security Law, Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: The Employment Security Program in Wyoming, 1952; Publication (Box 88, Folder 8)
- Box: 88, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Jobs for All, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 9)
    Author: University of Manitoba
- Box: 88, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Unemployment in Maryland, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 10)
    Author: Maryland Govenor's Committee on Employment Problems
- Box: 88, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: The Long-Term Unemployed in Mississippi, Publication (Box 88, Folder 11)
- Box: 88, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Reponse to Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank
  - Item 2: Unemployment and Work Force in New Hampshire, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
    Author: New Hampshire Department of Employment Security
  - Item 3: Unemployment and Work Force in New Hampshire, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Item 4: Unemployment and Work Force in New Hampshire, Publication (Box 88, Folder 12)
- Box: 88, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: What Happens to the Long-Term Unemployed, Publication (Box 88, Folder 13)
- Box: 88, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Education of Ohio's Unemployed, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Educational Attainment of Unemployed Beneficiaries in Ohio, Publication (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: the Education of the Unemployed in Ohio, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 14)
    Notes: October 31, 1965
- Box: 88, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Community Organization for Employment Development, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Item 2: Employee Displacement, Publication (Box 88, Folder 15)
- Box: 88, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Problem of Changeover Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 16)
- Box: 88, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Results of Tests on Measuring Under-Employment in Puerto Rico, Publication (Box 88, Folder 17)
    Author: Puerto Rico Department of Labor
  - Item 2: The Role of the Puerto Rico Department of Labor Under the Area Redevelopment Administration, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 17)
- Box: 88, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Relief of Destitute Unemployed, 1915; Publication (Box 88, Folder 18)
- Box: 88, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Government and the Unemployed, Publication (Box 88, Folder 19)
    Author: Public Administration Service
  - Item 2: Work, Relief and Security, 1941; Publication (Box 88, Folder 19)
    Author: U.S. Federal Works Agency
- Box: 88, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Winter Work, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 20)
    Author: Royal Bank of Canada
- Box: 88, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Seasonal Variations in Louisiana Employment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 21)
    Author: Kyou E. Choi
- Box: 88, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Seasonal Employment, 1967; Publication (Box 88, Folder 22)
    Author: Maine Legislature
- Box: 88, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Seasonal Employment, 1940; Publication (Box 88, Folder 23)
    Notes: February 1940
- Box: 88, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Structural Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
    Author: National Council for the Churches of Christ in the U.S.A.
  - Item 2: Research Study, 1967; Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
    Author: Jobs Now Project
    Notes: December 19, 1967
  - Item 3: Guidelines for Programs to Hire and Train Out-of-School Youth and the Hard-Core Unemployed, Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Research of Business and Industrial Firms that Employed Clients Referred by the Jobs Now Program, 1968; Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
    Author: James E. Murray
  - Item 5: The Nature of the Job Problem and the Role of New Public Service Employment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
    Author: Harold L. Sheppard
  - Item 6: The Special Impact Program in Los Angeles is Not Meeting Goal of Providing Jobs for the Disadvantaged, 1970; Publication (Box 88, Folder 24)
    Notes: October 7, 1970
- Box: 88, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Economic and Business Bulletin, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 25)
    Author: Temple University
  - Item 2: Marchant Moves South, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 25)
  - Item 3: New York State Employment Service and the Disadvantaged of New York City, Publication (Box 88, Folder 25)
- Box: 88, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 88, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Structural Unemployment, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 26)
- Box: 88, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Redundancy Payments Act, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 27)
  - Item 2: Industrial Transference Board Report, 1928; Publication (Box 88, Folder 27)
    Notes: July 1928
- Box: 88, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 88, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Unemployment and the Central City, 1968; Publication (Box 88, Folder 28)
    Author: Jesse E. Gloster
- Box: 88, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 88, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: The Relocation of the Hard Core Unemployed, 1968; Publication (Box 88, Folder 29)
    Author: Minneapolis Rehabilitation Center
- Box: 88, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 88, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: A Community Wide Approach to Training the Hard-Core, Publication (Box 88, Folder 30)
    Author: Ypsilanti Area Chamber of Commerce
- Box: 88, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 88, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: The Results of Employment Policy in Sweden, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 31)
    Author: Bertil Olsson
    Notes: June 15, 1961
- Box: 88, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Caught on the Horn of Plenty, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Item 2: Automation and Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Item 3: Experience of Other Countries in Dealing with Technological Unemployment, 1963; Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Item 4: Caught on the Horn of Plenty, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
  - Item 5: The Re-Employment Experience of Workers Displaced in the Closing of the American Viscose Plant, Publication (Box 88, Folder 32)
- Box: 88, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 88, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Case Studies of Displaced Workers, Publication (Box 88, Folder 33)
- Box: 88, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 88, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Machine-Made Jobs, Publication (Box 88, Folder 34)
- Box: 88, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Total Work Force, Employment, Unemployment, and Unemployment Rates, 1967; Publication (Box 88, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Estimates of the Total Work Force, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 35)
- Box: 88, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Facts About Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: John A. Ryan
  - Item 3: Unemployment in Prosperity, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia
  - Item 4: Unemployment, 1931; Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 5: Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 6: Persistent Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: W.E. Upjohn Institute
  - Item 7: The Flexible Work-Year, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 8: The Nature and Sources of Unemployment in the United States, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: Almqvist & Wiksell
  - Item 9: Emergency Employment Assistance Appropriation, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 10: Seven Keys to Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 11: Unemployment: The Nature of the Challenge, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 12: Population, Labor Force & Unemployment in Chronically Depressed Areas, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Item 13: The Structure of Unemployment in Areas of Substantial Labor Surplus, 1960; Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Notes: January 30, 1960
  - Item 14: The Rise of Chronic Unemployment, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: National Planning Association
  - Item 15: The Realities of Unemployment, Publication (Box 88, Folder 36)
    Author: Harry L. Hopkins
- Box: 88, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Recent Research on Creative Approaches to Environmental Stress, Publication (Box 88, Folder 37)
    Author: Iowa State University
  - Item 2: Methods of Forecasting Short Term Unemployment Change, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 37)
    Author: Stanley Lebergott
  - Item 3: Who Are the Unemployed?, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: A Profile of Unemployment in the Early 1960's, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 37)
    Notes: May 18, 1961
- Box: 88, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: The Incidence of Unemployment by State and Regions, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 38)
    Author: Edward F. Denison
    Notes: September 19, 1962
- Box: 88, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Sharper Look at Unemployment in U.S. Cities and Slums, Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 2: Unemployment in Major Areas, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: Unemployment Statistics: Meaning and Measurement, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
    Author: Raymond T. Bowman & Margaret E. Martin
  - Item 4: Unemployment Experience of Small and Large Firms, 1961; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
    Author: U.S. Deparment of Labor
  - Item 5: The Unemployed: Why They Started Looking for Work, 1965; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 6: How the Government Measures Unemployment, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 7: How the Government Measures Unemployment, 1962; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Item 8: The Anatomy of Unemployment, 1964; Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)
    Notes: May 8, 1964
  - Item 9: A Sharper Look at Unemployment in U.S. Cities and Slums, Publication (Box 88, Folder 39)